http://www.troutnut.com/privacy-policy

Aquatic Insect Encyclopedia
Fly Fishing Forum
User
Password
or register.
Scientific name search:
Troutnut.com Privacy Policy
Long story short:
Troutnut.com respects your privacy and won't give out or sell your email address or other information to anyone, and we have a pretty secure database so it's not likely to be stolen.
Like half the other sites on the Intenret, we use some advertisements by Google and Amazon, and they use "cookies" to store some basic information about where you've been so they can serve you more relevant ads.
This is no different here than on Google or Amazon themselves, or on all the other sites that use their ads.
However, Google does require that I have a privacy policy explaining this, so I downloaded a standard one and here it is:
Privacy Policy for www.troutnut.com
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at jason@troutnut.com.
At www.troutnut.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.troutnut.com and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, www.troutnut.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userÕs movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.troutnut.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.troutnut.com.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.troutnut.com and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....
Google Adsense
Amazon
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.troutnut.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.troutnut.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.troutnut.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Top 10 Fly HatchesBaetisBaetidaeEphemerellidaeHexagenia limbataChironomidaeHeptageniidaeEphemerella subvariaIsonychiaEphemerellaHydropsychidaeTop Gift Shop DesignsI outfish my daddy!Electric blue Hendrickson dun.I love buggers.
Big, green, wooly ones.I outfish my husband!Be the trout.
Eat mayflies.Top Insect SpecimensBaetisca obesa Mayfly NymphCorydalus Hellgrammite LarvaRhyacophila fuscula Caddisfly LarvaNeophylax Caddisfly AdultPteronarcys biloba Stonefly NymphMiscellaneous SitesDalton Highway (Haul Road) Corridor Map
Troutnut.com is copyright © 2004-2020 Jason
Neuswanger (email Jason). See my FAQ for information about use of my images.
privacy policy
